We'll talk about where we're seeing action.
If we look at the list of top gainers in Nifty 50,
we're seeing a rise of around 1.5% in SBI Life just before the results.
We'll also tell you what your strategy should be before the results. What levels should you keep in mind? Before that, let's find out
what expectations are being raised. Harsh has joined us with all this information about the results of
SBI Life and HDFC Life.
Harsh, please tell me, yes, so
when we talk about HDFC Life,
in gross theory, the income will expand by 25% to around Rs
18,000 crore. That
particular number packs around Rs 50,080 crore. 60%
expansion is what you're talking about. On your basis,
PV and margins will see an expansion.
Sequentiality's 29% VNB margin number
and PNB is expected at Rs 1,100 crore,
which is a 20% expansion. Are
stronger trends
non-par expected?  The tax exemptions that have been
removed will have an impact
in this particular quarter and
especially in March,
strong trends will be seen in HDFC Life's numbers. With regard to
growth, the
new product launches in 2024 will be
watched by investors because that
particular metric will drive growth going forward,
so they will keep an eye on it and will
also keep an eye on the persistence of investors.
When it comes to profitability, it is
expected to be around Rs
21,500 crore in 23%. That particular number,
profit after tax is expected to be around Rs 830 crore. It will
expand by 25%.
On your basis, VNB is expected to have a solid
expansion of 30% and VNB margins will be
solid around 29%. When it comes to
expectations, SBI Life will
further strengthen its graphical access and distribution network to
increase its growth engine in this particular quarter
and going forward also, new business
premium will be sustained.  It will do so but the important
metric is how SBI Life does its trading on non-performing assets,
that particular test will
come in due course and investors will have a look at how its margins and VNB will be.
Secondly, of course, there are
changes in tax regulations, will there be
changes in the products going forward, will there be any new
products available,
investors will also have a look at that.
To make the information accessible to the audience, it
is possible that there will be an increase of about 25% in the gross premium of HDFC Life and if we
talk about SBI Life, then here the company's
profit can be seen increasing by 23% every year
and along with this, there is an expectation of a
23% increase in the gross premium as well, so the
results are looking good
this time, but Vinay
would like to understand once how you are seeing,
you are seeing the setup forming on the charts of both SBI Life and HDFC Life,
good afternoon, so I will share the meaning of HDFC Life,
so in SBI Life we ​​are seeing that it has increased from
approximately 1000 to 60
A strong base is formed in the 1080 range
and this trend has reduced from there.
Gradually, an accumulation phase is going on in it. It
seems like the story is not a story, so the
level of 1060 to 1080 is something that investors should keep in mind. I have been
watching for the last approximately 2 months, so these
levels have been holding and trying to
hold it. If we were talking about resistance, then
first I am seeing a position registered at the
level of 1175. 1175,
which is the 200-day extension moving average, has the
power to hold as a resistance.
If this level of 1175 is crossed,
then we can expect a big upset in it.
But right now, an
accumulation phase is going on,
a strong base of 60 has been formed. As long as this
level is not broken on a closing basis, then
we can hope that there will be an upset
moment here in the coming two days. So,
SBI Life  But Vinay, you have shared your view,
but Kunal, we will take a view on HDFC Life from these
bastards. Since we are going to
know the results of Nifty, today there is Maruti's
Vinay ji, today there are results from Bajaj Finance as well,
so there are estimates about these as well,
how will the figures come, where should your focus be, this is
also to be known, but first
Vinay, you tell me, Kunal, you tell me that
HDFC Life has always been seen as a lion, there was
some good relief from RBI
regarding the stock of HDFC Bank, and today
also there is a little black cluster performance
because this lion is moving, what would be your advice
regarding HDFC Life before the results,
and if someone needs to set a stop loss to
protect against any shock, then what would that be?
24. We have talked about this entire segment many times
before that this
segment is in a long consolidation and in
fact the counters are doing very well.
From a position point of view, if we
talk about recent behavior, we
saw a high of around 620 in HDFC Life in January at the
time of the budget because of the debt announcement, and the
entire segment sold off.  I have already felt that
in the selloff, this counter had made a bottom of around 450 years
and further on, if
we count this entire reversal, then the 500
year level which comes at 61.8% is its strongest
resistance and the counter has
made it at the same level two days ago, so at the time being,
if someone has a long position in this counter, then
a stopper will be made at 515
and can be closed from its base and if
someone does not have a position, then it will be
advisable to avoid this counter for the time being,
if it crosses above the counter, then
we can again see levels up to 620/25,
advisory wise, we can get a story up to 500 level in this decline.